http://www.netaffinity.com/privacy.html

Products
Products
We offer thoughtfully crafted products that exceed the industry standard
Booking Engine
A booking engine based on the highest standards, built to convert and empower
Learn More
Website Builder
Built to ensure that your hotel website never goes out of date
Learn More
Hotel Gift Vouchers
Easy-to-use platform that enables you to customise and sell vouchers
Services
Our services are carefully crafted and executed in pursuit of one goal: direct bookings
Client Services
A team of hard-working, dedicated experts from the hospitality industry
Learn More
Bespoke Websites
Beautifully designed sites that are fully optimised by our team of experts
Learn More
Digital Marketing
A team of digital marketers armed with all the knowledge & tools you need
Learn More
Resources
Resources
Blogs, podcasts, webinars and more to support our customers in dynamic and helpful ways
Blog
Updated weekly with expert takes on current trends and developments of the industry
Learn More
Podcasts & Webinars
Listen to or sign up for all the latest tips, tricks and industry insights
Learn More
Knowledge Base
Access some helpful guides, how-to's and updates on all our products via our Knowledge Base
Learn More
Learning Academy
Become a certified expert in our products! Upskill and test your knowledge on our Academy
Learn More
About Us
About Us
Get to know our story, our team, our industry partners and the success of our clients.
About Us
Our story, values and team, plus everything in between. Our culture is important to us.
Learn More
News
Access all of our latest updates, some insightful industry news and events we host and attend.
Learn More
Case Studies
Our products deliver tangible results for clients. Read about the success of our clients.
Learn More
Partners
We work with a long list of talented partners to ensure our clients can make the most out of their products.
Net Affinity © 2000-2020
2nd Floor Block 4, Bracken Business Park,
Bracken Road, Sandyford,
Privacy Statement
Net Affinity is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
This Privacy Statement sets out how we use and protect any information that you give us or that we collect when you use our website www.netaffinity.com and our sub-domains blog.netaffinity.com; support.netaffinity.com
It is important that you read this Privacy Statement together with any other privacy notice or fair processing notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing your personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This Privacy Statement supplements the other notices and is not intended to override them. We reserve the right to update this Privacy Statement from time to time and as required. This version was last updated on 24 May 2018 and historic versions can be obtained by contacting us directly.
Who are we?
Net Affinity is the Data Controller, and this means that we determine how your personal data is processed and for what purposes. We are committed to best practice in all matters arising vis Data Protection including but not exclusively compliance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”) and Irish Data Protection legislation and have adopted an approach of review of changing laws and attitudes regarding Privacy and Data in order to implement such policy.
NET AFFINITY LIMITED
2nd Floor, Block, 4 Bracken Rd
Sandyford
Dublin D18 V0Y0
DUBLIN 18
TEL: +353 1 293 9906
EMAIL: PRIVACY@NETAFFINITY.COM
WEBSITE: WWW.NETAFFINITY.COM
To exercise all relevant rights, queries or complaints, our Data Privacy Representative can be contacted at privacy@netaffinity.com
What is personal data?
We may collect information from our users at several different points on our website.
This information may include:
Identity Data includes first name, last name, username or similar identifying data.
Contact Data includes address, email address, contact number or similar contact data.
Technical Data includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this website.
Usage Data includes information about how you use our website, products and services.
Marketing and Communications Data includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and your communication preferences.
We do not collect any Special Categories of personal data about you (this includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data). Nor do we collect any information about criminal convictions and offences.
We also collect, use and share aggregated data such as statistical or demographic data for analytical purposes. Aggregated data may be derived from your personal data but is not considered personal data in law as this data does not directly or indirectly reveal your identity. All such data will be anonymised. In the event that that we do combine or connect aggregated data with your personal data so that it can directly or indirectly identify you, we treat the combined data as personal data which will be used in accordance with this Privacy Statement.
How do we collect your personal data?
We use different methods to collect data from and about you through:
Direct interactions
You may give us your Identity, Contact, Marketing and Communications data by filling in forms, corresponding with us directly (this includes email, phone, letter and other forms of communication), utilising our Blog, utilising our Live Chat and/or contacting us directly in any similar way.
Automated technologies/interactions
As you interact with our website, we may automatically collect Technical and Usage data about your equipment, browsing actions and/or patterns. We collect this personal data by using cookies, server logs and other similar technologies.
How do we process your personal data?
We will only use your personal data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances:
Where you have sent us a message by completing the “Get in Touch” form on our website
Where you have sent us an email, written to us or telephoned us by using our “Contact Us” details page
Where you have asked us to provide you with a service or product
Where you have initiated a live chat with us or raised a support ticket
Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests
Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation
Generally, we do not rely on consent as a legal basis for processing your personal data other than in relation to sending direct marketing communications to you via email which you have the right to withdraw at any time by clicking the Unsubscribe button in marketing emails or by contacting us directly.
Our website includes a link to our Blog sub-domain the processes of which is covered by this Privacy Statement.
Our website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their Privacy Statements. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the Privacy Statements of every website you visit.
Why do we process your personal data?
We may process your personal data for more than one lawful ground depending on the specific purpose for which we are using your data. The legal bases we rely on to process your personal data includes Consent, Legitimate Interest, Contractual Relationship and Legal Obligation. On these bases, we use your personal for one or more of the following purposes:
To respond to your enquiry and/or message
To manage our relationship with you
To respond to your support query and/or request for assistance
To send you marketing material via email
To add you to our subscribers list
To process an application for one of our vacancies
To send you news releases, publications and updates
What cookies do we use?
Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to allow websites to function, improve efficiency and performance. In addition, cookies are also used to provide information to us in order to measure the effectiveness of our online presence, to determine the path users take on our site and to identify repeat visitors of our site. We do not use cookies to gather personal identifying or contact data. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when websites set or access cookies. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this website may become inaccessible or not function properly. Full details regarding the cookies we use can be found in our Cookie Policy
Do we share your personal data?
In certain circumstance, we may need to share personal data in compliance with and in pursuit of legitimate company interests e.g. the use of processors to manage communications, chat widgets, surveys or the secure storage of your data. We require all third parties to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third-party service providers to use your personal data for their own purposes and only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.
Do we transfer your personal data internationally?
All personal data is stored within the European Economic Area or countries that have been designated as adequate by the European Commission. We will not transfer any data to a third country or international organisation without your explicit consent and without appropriate privacy safeguards in place.
How do we protect your personal data?
We comply with our obligations under the “GDPR” by storing and destroying personal data securely; by protecting personal data from loss, misuse, unauthorised access and disclosure; and by ensuring that appropriate technical measures are in place to protect personal data.
How long do we keep your personal data?
We comply with our obligations under the “GDPR” by not collecting or retaining excessive amounts of data and will only retain your personal data for as long as is necessary to fulfil our legal obligations or for the purposes we collected it for. We keep data in accordance with the guidance set out within our formal records retention policies and do not maintain data beyond your consent of what is absolutely required by law.
What are your rights over your personal data?
You have the following rights with respect to your personal data: -
The right to request a copy of your personal data which we hold about you.
The right to request that we correct any personal data if it is found to be inaccurate, incomplete or out-of-date.
The right to request your personal data is erased where it is no longer necessary or lawful for us to retain such data.
If we have required your consent to process data, you have the right to withdraw your consent to the processing at any time.
The right to request that we provide the you with your personal data and in certain circumstances, to transmit that data directly to another data controller.
The right, where there is a dispute in relation to the accuracy or processing of your personal data, to request a restriction is placed on further processing.
The right to object to the processing of personal data, where:
- we rely on legitimate interests as the legal basis for processing
- we are using the data for direct marketing
- we are processing data for the purposes of scientific/historical research and statistics
The right to lodge a complaint with the Supervisory Authority which in respect of us is the:
The Data Protection Commissioner
Canal House, Station Road, Portarlington, Co. Laois, Ireland
Tel: +353 (0) 761 104 800
Email: info@dataprotection.ie
All of these rights can be availed of free of charge.
Latest Version: 24th May 2018
Net Affinity © 2000-2020
2nd Floor Block 4, Bracken Business Park,
Bracken Road, Sandyford,
